hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and I'm excited that
you're here today listening to this um
again if this is your first time
listening to our podcast I've been
helping mentors and coaches for over 22
years to scale their businesses to
multiple seven and eight figures and I
bring strategies to you in this podcast
that you can use that you can apply
right now this week to get results I
want to talk about growing your email
list growing your email list is the
number one thing that will affect your
bottom line in your coaching or online
course business it's the number one
indicator of success they say on average
you should be able to make at least a
dollar to $2 a month per person on your
email list which is why it'd be
incredible to have an email list of
8,000 10,000 20,000 people in fact when
we built businesses that were seven
figures we had over 100,000 people on
those email lists doing that now you
don't even need that many people on your
email list to be able to make seven
figures I've actually been able to make
seven figures in our business with only
4,000 people on the email list by
leveraging each relationship that we
have through the email list but growing
my email list is the number one thing
that determines the long-term growth and
the trajectory of that and so in your
business that's what you want to do and
we don't just want names on an email
list we want people that we can nurture
a connection with that we can build a
relationship with long term now how do
we build a relationship with your email
list well once somebody joins your email
list you send them content in the form
of videos YouTube videos is one of the
best ways that I know that can do this
because YouTube has a great algorithm
where once somebody starts watching one
or two of your videos it starts to send
them all of the videos that you start to
have especially when they subscribe so
it's really a great way to nurture and
it kind of TAPS into a double whammy
with the way the algorithm on YouTube
works one of my favorite things to do is
to send people YouTube videos that I've
created even our podcast you might be
watching this right now because I sent
you an email with this episode of this
podcast and and that's exactly how it
works is again we create offers that
people use to join our email list you
can make a number of different offers
whether it be like an ebook offer
whether it be a webinar whether it be a
challenge offer something like that that
grows the email list it promises some
kind of a big outcome to people that
they can get in exchange for the name
and email address now of course not
everybody who signs up on your email
list is going to open all your emails
you're not going to click everything
that you send them they're not going to
be committed longterm to that
relationship with you but it's important
to make sure that as you build your
business that you make growing your
email list an important part of that
process we can get bogged down in our
businesses doing all the stuff that we
have to do every single day from
coaching our clients to helping them get
results and those things are important
but making your efforts being concerted
towards growing your email list is one
of the top things that we need to do so
we need to figure out what are the
things that the people that are going to
buy bu your coaching programs buy your
courses what do they desire the most
what is the number one thing that they
can get a quick win with you on and then
you create some kind of valuable content
in the form of video ebook something
like that that they can sign up for to
join your email list with and so in that
as well you don't just give value but
you also use it as a way to present your
offer to people use it as a way to
present your coaching program and this
is the foundation of the system that I
teach people in my wealthy coach Academy
this is the foundation of everything
that works when it comes to online
marketing is is that as you start to
grow your email list whether you're
running ads or you're doing organic
content you're using that as a way to
present your paid offers to people
having a paid offer in the form of a
coaching program the form of a group
coaching a membership something that you
can do that's Evergreen something that
is not going to burn you out something
that's not going to take a ton of your
time something that can allow you to
actually work on your business instead
of in your business and be a true
entrepreneur that's an important part of
this and so having lead magnets that
grow your email list is the top thing
that we need to do so we grow our email
list and then we turn that into forms of
communication and generally these forms
of communication are going to be
automated pre-recorded things that you
can record once and send out to a wide
group of people I can get over 200
people to watch a video presentation of
mine in just a week using an email list
growing training that I create on on a
video training and then in that I can do
a small offer to try out my wealthy
coach Academy to join to get bonuses to
save money on that and that's what has
grown our business and added 10 to 20
brand new people inside of our business
every single month and that's exactly
what you need to do as well if you're a
coach if you're a mentor if you're a
trainer and you've been trying to scale
things you've been trying to get the
kind of clients that you want you got to
grow your email list having an
irresistible offer that grows the email
list is about knowing exactly what
people desire and what is preventing
them and blocking them from getting to
that desire everything that we do in our
marketing is this is that we mirror back
to the person who is best likely to
become our prospects and our clients we
take internally what is the internal
dialogue that they are using in their
own minds every single person has an
internal dialogue of struggle and
frustration but also desire and dreams
and visions and goals and if we can
mirror back to them that we see that
Vision that we understand it that we
know where they're coming from and you
can do this you don't need to be a mind
reader nobody's a mind reader but as you
start to connect with people we also use
artificial intelligence to help us
brainstorm a lot of these ideas and be
able to actually understand and get into
the mind of our Prospect it works even
better than having to interview
thousands and thousands of people to be
able to do that so when we can virtually
get into the mind of our Prospect and
understand by putting ourselves in their
shoes
virtually we are able to mirror back to
them exactly what those desires are and
that becomes the promise of what we
deliver in the results of our coaching
so you end up promising the very thing
that they desire the most and you do
that in your lead magnets as well
whatever lead magnet topic that you're
using now one of the best ways to come
up with ideas for your lead magnets
here's one of the things and that's a
big unlock that I've taught my clients
is is that if you start looking at
content in the topic of your Niche other
pages on social media Instagram Facebook
going to different websites looking up
on YouTube videos on the same topic
looking in the description of those
YouTube videos and then clicking on
those links what you will start to
notice is do that a little bit maybe
take like 30 minutes to do that on as
many competitor Pages or sites as you
can in their offers their lead magnets
and we're going to do two things number
one I want you to pay attention to the
lead magnets that they're running to
grow their email lists and I want you to
make note of it I actually copy and
paste all of the text of my competitors
to a document that I can have that I can
pull from a swipe file is what we call
it that we can pull from to be able to
look at to come up with ideas for our
offers and I even end up joining my
competitor's email list because now I
have an email account I have a private
email account that I use that nobody
else uses that gets all of these emails
from my competitors that they end up
sending me and I can look at them to
come up with ideas for offers hooks
sales copy angles to Market in my
business and this is one of the ways
that I don't have to work very hard is
because I just let my competitors kind
of do the work for me and then I figure
out okay which one aligns with the type
of prospect that I want to reach and
then I take their sales copy and their
offers and I reward it in my own
language I use it as a model to reward
those offers in my own language I'm not
copying the content I'm not copying the
the testimonies or the claims or and I'm
not duplicating their landing pages no
but I'm using the text the written text
in the emails and the offers that I
receive my from my competitors their
landing pages I'm using the written text
the writing as a template that I can
then what I like to do is go into Ai and
have the AI rewrite some of those
headlines and then I will start to edit
and modify those and then put those up
on a landing page for an offer that I
create okay the other side of it that we
can do is is that as you do this not
only do you get ideas for your offers
and landing pages and
copy Facebook and Instagram ads
particularly will start to show you ads
of your competitors that you can see and
so you can start to see what your
competitors are actually investing into
advertising for if somebody's investing
into advertising there's a reason why
they're doing that because it's
converting for them and it's turning
into sales and so you can have a lot of
confidence doing this in your own
business by figuring out okay what are
my competitors advertising and promoting
and marketing and it'll give you ideas
as far as the topics to use for what
you're doing a lot of times you can use
AI to come up with the topics but then
what I like to do is I like to look at
okay what are my competitors doing and
then I can use the AI to refine
additional ideas artificial intelligence
is one of the best tools that we can use
when it comes to creating our marketing
materials creating our sales materials
creating the stuff that's going to
connect with people online it it's
extremely intelligent at the ability to
write marketing language and when it
comes to your marketing language on your
sales copy your your your emails that
you send out the way that you're
actually marketing your offers to people
we don't need to be the one that comes
up with all the stuff original ourselves
we can Outsource it to these tools and
be able to use these tools to
effectively connect with our prospects
and find the people that we can truly
help online and this is what leads them
into our email list and then allows you
to be able to sell to those people when
you promote offers to them now one of my
favorite tools again when it comes to
email list marketing and selling is I
got two books that I love I I mention
these all the time to my clients number
one The Ultimate Sales letter by Dan
Kennedy attract and boost new sales this
one is all about writing sales copy and
then number two this one's more on
traditional sales straight line selling
the way of the Wolf by Jordan Belfor one
of the best sales books that I know I
use this for uh group modeling and group
sales but there's incredible Concepts
that are actually written in this book
about not doing sleazy sales doing it
very authentically doing it in a way
that works and that's really effective
I've read the book like six times and I
find it to be one of the most
foundational pieces to what actually
works when it comes to Marketing Online
so those are some resources for you to
check out uh those are some ways that
can do that now again in my wealthy
coach Academy program we work with
people every single week in their
businesses in this Mastermind to be able
to get them results to be able to show
them exactly what it takes to be able to
become a wealthy coach to be able to
make six and even seven figures in their
business so again I'd love to see you in
this program with us to join us in here
you can find a link below they can give
you some information on that we'll talk
soon everybody
[Music]
[Applause]